<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Tillery</title>
    <link>https://tillery.fyi/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Tillery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tillery.fyi/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Work Coming Out Email</title>
      <link>https://tillery.fyi/blog/all-hands_namechange/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tillery.fyi/blog/all-hands_namechange/</guid>
      <description>In case it&amp;rsquo;s helpful in someone else&amp;rsquo;s experience, below is the email I sent to the internal all-hands email at work regarding my name change.
 GRIMM family,
For those of you that want to skip to the end, here&amp;rsquo;s the short form: My name is now Tillery, and I use they/them pronouns. Email address and public key are changing.
As many of you already know, about a year ago I came out as non-binary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A more up to date bio</title>
      <link>https://tillery.fyi/blog/updating-bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tillery.fyi/blog/updating-bio/</guid>
      <description>Hello, Internet! This is the long-form version of the about me twitter thread I posted.
There are a lot of things that I am, and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what order to put them into. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of taxonomies when they apply to other things, but bad at labels when they come to me. I guess I&amp;rsquo;ll just get started.
Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Tillery! I&amp;rsquo;m non-binary and use they/them pronouns. When I first realized I was non-binary and came out, I identified as demimale and used he or they interchangeably - that isn&amp;rsquo;t the case anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Defcon thoughts, 2019</title>
      <link>https://tillery.fyi/blog/post-defcon_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tillery.fyi/blog/post-defcon_2019/</guid>
      <description>Last night, after the last day of DEF CON 27, a group of GRIMM and Scythe folks were unwinding at one of our short term rental houses. At some point during the night, Dan LaVoie suggested we go around the circle and each say the best thing about the week for us.
I elected to go last, and now I&amp;rsquo;m electing to share mine with you all.
Like most of the folks that told their favorite things, mine is a bit of a rant, listing several positives, but it leads to my final point, so stick with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me (outdated)</title>
      <link>https://tillery.fyi/blog/oldabout/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tillery.fyi/blog/oldabout/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: This post is outdated. It remains here for historical curiosity only. For an up-to-date look at who I am, check out the about page. Hello friends, family, and the internet at large!
For a small handful of you, this isn&amp;rsquo;t news, but for some of you it is. I wanted to do this in a way that gave me a chance to find my words, and also share this information with everyone I care about in one place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
